# **Minal Bombatkar**

# **UX** Designer

https://minalbombatkar.co



## Contact:

Nuremberg, Germany 90429 +49 15163657851

bombatkar.minal@gmail.com

<u>github.com/bombatkar-minal</u> linkedin.com/in/minal-bombatkar

#### Technical Skills:

Wireframe tools Prototyping tools Illustrator, Invision studio Figma, Sketch Balsamic HTML, CSS, JS WordPress

#### **UX Skills**:

Business requirements analysis
User analysis and user research
Personas
Customer journeys
Concept ideation
Information architecture
User flows
Wireframes
Prototyping
User testing
Mockups
Product development life cycle

# Certifications:

Accenture - Digital Skills User Experience
CAREERFOUNDRY Fundamentals of UX
LinkedIn learning Illustrator for Web Design
Wireframing

Scrum planning and meeting

Driven by the challenge to create simple, intuitive user experiences from conception to development. Able to execute all phases of the design process: Research, conceptual design, prototyping, validating, production-ready designs, usability testing and implementation. Experience in the product development life-cycle of web and mobile applications.

# **Experience:**

## **E-learning Course Designer**

eNyota Ltd | May 2016 - Jun 2017 | India

Experience with course designing, web-based training, and E-Learning content development using Adobe Captivate, Articulate Storyline

#### **Assistant Professor**

VCACS College | Jan 2013 - Nov 2013 | India

Experience with course designing, web-based training, and E-Learning content development using Adobe Captivate, Articulate Storyline

Fulltime Mother | Dec 2013 - April 2016

#### **Education:**

CAREERFOUNDRY | March 2019 - Present | Germany

During the course, specializing in UX fundamentals and methodology, data and research-driven approaches to design, as well as prototyping, wireframing and website optimization.

During this program, I designed a vocabulary mobile app called "Lexis" from scratch while utilizing best practices of UX design. Develop and prototype design solutions, not only to communicate ideas and concepts but to test with real customers to encourage collaboration and iterative processes.

# German language certification

linguademia | May 2018 - Jan 2019 | Germany

German up to level B1: Fulltime course for 8 months and achieved the certificate of completion.

## **Master of Technology**

NMU | Aug 2009 - Sep 2011 | India

Nanotechnology, Quantum Machines, Applied physics

## **Master of Science**

NMU | Aug 2007 - Jun 2009 | India

Information technology, Web development, Programming language

#### **Bachelor of Science**

Amravati University | Jun 2004 – Jun 2007 | India Computer Science, Mathematics, Statistics